#### JERRY KIMBRELL

83 SE Carters Pl Lawton, OK 73501 Phone: 580 591-1281 jerry.kimbrell@yahoo.com

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Seeking a position with a company that supports the Government of the United States, who will benefit from more than 26 years of success, leadership experience, and instructional excellence by demonstrating outstanding interpersonal communication skills, and a drive for excellence with superb customer service

# **SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS**

Over 9 years of professional Supervisory Human Resources experience with the United States Army, and Oklahoma Army National Guard, handling personnel records, payroll, promotions, reductions, assignments for more than 700 personnel. Responsible for development and implementation of plans, policies and standard operating procedures, along with developing and implementing training models, classes and other educational techniques. Charged with the precision and accuracy of all data for tracking and reporting to the highest levels of supervisory panels, committees, and individuals.

# **SUPERVISOR**

**HUMAN RESOURCES** Organized, trained, supervised and led a Human resources staff of 17 personnel. Proficient in all Microsoft Office programs including Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint, One Note, and Publisher. Possess the ability to master any web-based program or job-specific database program with little to no supervision. Written and verbal skills are outstanding. Awarded high honors and accolades for 100% accuracy on more than 700 personnel, medical, and training records.

### PERSONNEL **SUPERVISOR**

Possess outstanding leadership skills and abilities with special emphasis on training and teaching. Have supervised and led up to 45 Personnel in high and low stress environments. Certified as a U.S. Army Instructor specializing in numerous areas of importance. Taught more than one thousand classes, with outstanding results.

## **BUSINESS OWNER OPERATOR**

Expert on documentation, filing, tracking dollars spent plus payroll using QuickBooks, and QuickBooks Pro. Multitasking skills are unmatched

#### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

- · Administrative Manager/ FSO, FXCX Inc. January 2015- Present
- Owner/Operator, RAW Earth Landscaping and Construction May2014 –December 2014
- Human Resources Supervisor, Oklahoma Army National Guard, Fort Sill, OK, January 2012 - January 2014
- Senior Wheeled Vehicle Mechanic, Oklahoma Army National Guard, Hobart, OK, August 2008 - January 2012
- · Armament Maintenance Supervisor, Oklahoma Army National Guard, Fort. Sill, OK, June 2007 August 2008
- Police Officer, Department of the Army Federal Police, Fort Sill, OK, May, 2005-June 2007
- · Howitzer Section Chief, US Army (Paladin)
- · February, 2002- March 2003
- · Field Artillery Instructor, March 2003-April 2004

#### **EDUCATION**

- HVAC Technician, Air Conditioning and Refrigeration, Great Plains Technology Center, Lawton, OK, 2013
- Bachelor of Science, Theology and Religion, Southwestern College, Winfield, KS, <u>2016</u>
- Military Occupational Specialty, Wheeled Vehicle Mechanic, RTSM, Army National Guard, Salina, KS, 2006
- · Military Occupational Specialty, 13B Cannon Crewmember,
- · Fort Sill, OK 1997
- · U.S Army Instructor Training Fort Sill, Oklahoma 2003